so far we've heard a lot of good things
到目前为止，我们已经听到了很多好消息
about VCG and for good reason but VCG
关于VCG，并且有很好的理由，但是VCG
also has some important limitations that
也有一些重要的限制
this video will introduce you to the
该视频将向您介绍
first is that VCG requires that the
首先是VCG要求
agents tell the mechanism everything
代理告诉机制一切
about their private information this is
关于他们的私人信息，这是
fine if we really believe our model that
如果我们真的相信我们的模型，那很好
the agents have utility only for the
代理商仅对
choice that the mechanism makes and the
机制做出的选择和
payments that are imposed but in some
强制性付款，但在某些情况下
settings agents might interact together
设置代理可能会相互作用
repeatedly and telling the mechanism and
反复地告诉机制
publicizing something about their
宣传他们的东西
private information might affect their
私人信息可能会影响他们的
ability to compete in future
未来竞争能力
interactions so if that's true the
互动，如果是真的，
agents might prefer a mechanism in which
代理人可能更喜欢一种机制
only as much information is disclosed as
仅披露与
is required to actually compute the
需要实际计算
social welfare maximizing choice and the
社会福利最大化的选择和
VCG payments this is often possible and
VCG付款通常是可能的，并且
VCG requires revealing more than that so
VCG要求揭示更多
in such cases a VCG wouldn't be a good
在这种情况下，VCG并不是一个好选择
choice of mechanism here's something a
机制的选择这是一个
little bit more subtle about VCG it
关于VCG有点微妙
turns out to be susceptible to collusion
事实证明容易串通
so let's look at the road building game
让我们来看一下筑路游戏
here we have three agents we're gonna
在这里，我们有三个特工
choose to build the road rather than not
选择修路而不是不修路
building the road because we get utility
建立道路，因为我们获得了效用
of 300 for building the road and 250 for
300修路，250
not building it Hey look if we look at
没有建立它，嘿，看看我们
the agents VCG payments let's look for
代理商的VCG付款让我们寻找
example at agent 1 he would be paid a
例如，在代理商1处，他将获得报酬
hundred because in the situation where
一百，因为在这种情况下
he exists agent 2 as happiness of a
他将代理2作为a的幸福存在
hundred and he's gonna have to pay 250
一百，他要付250
because in the world where he doesn't
因为在世界上他不
exist the road won't be built and
存在的道路不会被修建，
they'll be agent 3 we'll have 250 units
他们将成为代理3我们将拥有250个单位
of utility so in other words he's going
实用，换句话说，他要去
to be paid a hundred and have to pay 250
付一百，必须付250
which means that his payment is going to
这意味着他的付款将
be a hundred and fifty well we know that
要一百五十点，我们知道
that he has a dominant strategy to tell
他有一个占主导地位的策略来告诉
the truth but what if both agent one and
事实是事实，但是如果两个代理都
two could coordinate to change their
两个可以协调改变他们的
declared valuations what if for example
申报的估价，例如
they were each to increase their
他们每个人都增加他们的
valuation by fifty dollars
估价五十美元
well in this situation it actually turns
在这种情况下，它实际上变成
out that both agents one two are better
可以看出，两个代理商一人比较好
off their payments both go down by $50
他们的付款都下降了50美元
how does that happen well it turns out
结果如何发生
that agent to change of declaration
该代理更改声明
reduces the payment for agent one and
减少代理一的付款，并
agent ones change of declaration reduces
代理人的申报变更减少
the payment for agent two so if they can
代理二的付款，以便他们可以
collude together they can both reduce
在一起可以减少
their payments this doesn't violate our
他们的付款不违反我们的
claim that they have individual dominant
声称他们有个人主导
strategies but it is a problem for VCG
策略，但这是VCG的问题
so we have to be sure that we don't use
所以我们必须确保不使用
VCG in situations where it's easy for
VCG在容易发生的情况下
agents to collude so the next problem
代理商勾结，所以下一个问题
with VCG that I'd like to tell you about
我想告诉您有关VCG的信息
is that the again has to do with the
是又与
payments and we say that VCG is not
付款，我们说VCG不是
frugal because the payments can can
节俭，因为付款可以
really see him out of line so let's
真的看不见他，所以让我们
think again about this graph routing
再考虑一下这个图形路由
example that we've seen before where we
我们在之前看到的例子
want to find the shortest path and pay
想要找到最短的路径并付款
agents for routing traffic along their
沿其路由流量的代理
edges so recall in this example that the
边缘，所以在此示例中回想起
shortest path is this one with a cost of
最短的路径是成本为
5 and recall also that the second
5，还记得第二
shortest path is this one with a cost of
最短的路径是成本为
6 right 2 + 3 + 1 now let's think in
6对2 + 3 + 1现在让我们思考
particular about the effect on agent a B
特别注意对试剂A B的影响
of changes to a C's cost and what I'm
C的成本变化和我的变化
going to end up showing you is that VCG
最终向您展示的是VCG
can end up paying arbitrarily more than
最终可能会任意支付比
a B is willing to accept because a B's
乙愿意接受，因为乙的
payment doesn't end up depending on his
最终付款取决于他的
own declaration but instead ends up
自己的声明，但最终以
depending on on the cost of the next
取决于下一个的成本
shortest path so and this is also a
最短的路径，这也是
possible problem in cases where we're
在我们遇到的情况下可能出现的问题
not paying the agents were rather where
不向代理商付款，而是在哪里
the agents are paying us so let's see
代理商付钱给我们，让我们看看
how it works so if for example the cost
它是如何工作的，例如成本
of this edge was to increase to 8 then
这个优势是增加到8
here our cost would be 12
这里我们的成本是12
our second shortest paths cost would be
我们的第二个最短路径成本是
12 and so that that would change the
12，这样就可以改变
payment to a B and it would go up by six
支付给乙，它将增加六
so we increased this value here of
所以我们在这里增加了这个值
somebody else's value by six and
别人的价值是六
although we didn't change anything about
虽然我们没有改变任何事情
what a B was willing to accept we ended
乙愿意接受什么，我们结束了
up changing our payment to a B also by
也将我们的付款更改为B
sex and indeed if the cost was any X
性别，如果费用是X
greater than to four for this edge AC
对于此边缘AC，大于四
then we would end up making a payment to
那么我们最终将付款给
a B which depends on X and doesn't
一个B取决于X并且不依赖于
depend on a B's own value so this means
取决于B自身的值，所以这意味着
that the gap between agents true costs
代理商之间的差距，真实成本
and the payments they could receive
以及他们可以收到的款项
under VCG is unbounded now we might
在VCG下是无界的，现在我们可能
think that we're just comparing to the
认为我们只是在与
wrong thing we might think that that we
错误的事情，我们可能会以为我们
really can't do anything about the fact
事实真的无能为力
that VCG is going to not be able to
VCG将无法
charge people based on their own values
根据自己的价值观向人们收费
but we might hope that VC G's payments
但我们可能希望VC G的付款
are close to the cost of the second
接近第二次的成本
shortest disjoint path and it turns out
最短的不相交路径，结果
that that's not even true so here's a
那甚至都不是真的，所以这是一个
different a little bit more complicated
不同一点更复杂
graph that will illustrate that point so
可以说明这一点的图表
here I have two disjoint paths this one
这里我有两条不相交的路径
here goes through K agents and each
这里经过K个代理商，每个
agent has a cost of C over K so K times
代理商的成本超过K，所以K倍
C over K means the total cost is C here
C超过K表示总成本为C
I have another edge with only one agent
我只有一个代理人有另一个优势
and his cost is C times 1 plus Epsilon
他的成本是C乘以1加Epsilon
so as long as Absalon is a positive
只要阿布萨隆是积极的
number the top path is going to be
编号的最高路径将是
shorter than the bottom path so VCG
比底部路径短，所以VCG
picks the top path and it pays each of
选择顶部路径，并支付每个
the K agents this amount here so it
K代理商在这里的数量，所以它
charges each of the K agents the costs
向K个代理商收取费用
of the other agents on the shortest path
最短路径上其他代理的数量
and then it pays them the utility there
然后向他们支付公用事业费
the cost of the guy who doesn't get
没有得到的人的代价
picked and if we just rearrange this to
选择，如果我们只是重新安排这个
a little bit of algebra and compute VG's
一点代数并计算VG
total payment by multiplying this amount
总付款额乘以该金额
by K
由K
you can confirm that this amount here is
您可以确认这里的金额是
VC G's total payment care well that's
VC G的总付款服务很好
kind of bad news because compare this
有点坏消息，因为比较一下
value here to this value and you'll see
将此值设置为该值，您将看到
that VC G's payment is theta of K times
VC G的付款是K倍的theta
the cost of the second shortest path so
第二条最短路径的成本
what that means is it differs only by a
这意味着它的区别仅在于
constant away from being K times bigger
不断远离K倍
and now we're comparing actually to the
现在我们实际上是在与
second shortest path so it really seems
第二条最短的路径，所以看来
like VCG can end up paying much more
像VCG最终可能要付出更多
than is sensible
比明智的
here's a fourth problem with vc g let's
这是vc g的第四个问题
think about the notion of revenue
考虑收入的概念
monotonicity this is a concept that
单调性这是一个概念
seems very intuitive and natural to us
对我们来说似乎很直观自然
for a mechanism that the revenue that a
对于一种机制，
mechanism would obtain would always
机制将永远获得
weakly increase as I add agents to the
当我将代理商添加到
mechanism so you might kind of
机制，所以您可能会
intuitively think that if I'm running a
凭直觉认为，如果我正在运行
mechanism it's always good to attract
机制总是吸引人
more participants to the mechanism
该机制的更多参与者
because that can only increase my
因为那只会增加我的
revenue but it turns out this isn't true
收入，但事实并非如此
under BCG so let's go back to the road
在BCG下，让我们回到路上
building example with different numbers
不同编号的建筑示例
here we see a case where the utility for
在这里，我们看到一种情况
building the road is a hundred the
修路是一百
aggregate utility the igrew utility for
汇总实用程序igrew实用程序用于
not building the road is ninety and so
不修路是九十等等
we would choose to build the road and we
我们会选择修路，而我们
would charge agent to 90 because that's
会向代理商收取90的费用，因为那是
the amount of utility that agent one
代理人的效用金额
would have if agent two wasn't around so
如果第二个特工不在身边的话
far so good but now let's consider
到目前为止还不错，但现在让我们考虑
adding another agent and in particular
添加另一个代理，尤其是
let's add an agent who has the same
让我们添加一个具有相同的代理
utility as agent two well this changes
实用程序作为代理两个很好的这种变化
everything because now if I drop either
一切，因为现在如果我放弃
agent 2 or agent 3 then I'm still going
特工2或特工3然后我仍然要走
to end up in a situation where I make
最终导致我
the same choice that means neither of
相同的选择意味着
these agents is pivotal and because
这些代理人至关重要，因为
they're not pivotal they don't pay
他们不是关键，他们不付钱
anything so now nobody has to pay
所以现在没有人要付钱
anything so what this means is that
所以这意味着什么
adding another agent to my mechanism
在我的机制中添加其他代理
didn't change the choice that was made
并没有改变所做的选择
by VC G but caused it to go from a
由VC G造成，但它来自
positive amount of revenue to zero
正收入为零
revenue another way of seeing why this
收入了解这种情况的另一种方式
could be a problem is
可能是一个问题
that agent too could pretend to be to
该特工也可能假装是
agents if he was able to submit a bid to
代理，如果他能够向
the mechanism under a false name and if
假名下的机制，如果
he could do that he could eliminate his
他可以做到，可以消除他的
own payment so with the the problem with
自己付款，所以有问题
collusion we've seen that if two agents
串通我们已经看到，如果有两个特工
can kind of behave like an one agent in
可以像一个代理商一样
VCG we've got a problem here we see that
VCG，这里有一个问题，我们看到
if one agent can behave like two agents
如果一个特工可以像两个特工一样
we've also got a problem here's one last
我们也有一个问题，这是最后一个
concern about VCG sometimes we might
对于VCG有时我们可能会担心
want to use the mechanism as in the road
想要在旅途中使用该机制
building example just as a way of making
建立例子，作为一种制作方式
a social choice not a in order to
社会选择不是为了
actually collect money from the agents
实际从代理商那里收钱
and if this is the case I might actually
如果是这种情况，我可能实际上
not really want to keep the money within
真的不想把钱存进去
the mechanism maybe even the mechanism
机制甚至机制
is just a computer program it's not even
只是计算机程序而已
something that's able to hold on to the
能够坚持下去的东西
money so I might like to rebate the
钱，所以我想回扣
money back to the agents somehow and the
钱以某种方式退还给代理商，
problem is that if I just give all of
问题是，如果我只给所有
the agents of rebate kind of no matter
返利的代理商无论如何
how I do it
我该怎么做
it ends up changing the agents
最终改变了代理商
incentives so the agents start behaving
激励，使代理开始行为
differently in order to change the
为了改变
amount of a rebate they get and it ends
他们得到的回扣数量到此为止
up breaking VCG so for example even if I
打破VCG，所以即使我
say I'm gonna take all of the profits
说我要拿走所有的利润
that VCG makes and give them to charity
由VCG制造并捐赠给慈善机构
well if the agents care about the
好，如果代理商关心
charity then they're gonna care about
慈善，然后他们会关心
what happened and that's gonna change
发生了什么，那将会改变
their utility or if I'm gonna just take
他们的效用，或者如果我要接受
the money and go down the street and buy
钱去街上买
myself something if that benefits the
我自己有什么好处
local economy and that benefits the
地方经济，这对
agents then that's going to give them
代理商然后这将给他们
new incentives so so kind of formally
新的激励措施如此正式
what I have to do is burn the money I
我要做的就是烧掉我的钱
have to take the money and just kind of
必须要拿钱，只是
destroy it in a way that has no
以一种没有的方式销毁它
consequences for the agents so that I
对代理商的后果，使我
don't give them the wrong incentives now
现在不要给他们错误的激励
I should give you a caveat it actually
我应该给你一个警告
is possible to return some of the
可以退还一些
revenues to the agents but it's very
收入给代理商，但这是非常
tricky to do this and and in general
一般而言，很难做到这一点
what's not possible is to return all of
不可能将所有
the money so there are there are ways of
钱，所以有办法
returning some fraction of the money
退还一部分钱
which is discussed in the literature but
在文献中有讨论，但是
in general it's not possible to just
一般来说，不可能只是
hand back all the money to the agents
把所有的钱还给代理商
so overall we've seen that despite the
因此总体而言，尽管
the great properties that VCG has there
VCG具有的出色性能
are also some caveats with it now I
我现在也有一些注意事项
should mention that some of these
应该提到其中一些
caveats are problems with mechanisms
注意事项是机制的问题
other than VCG as well so although I've
除了VCG以外，尽管我已经
pointed out some problems here I don't
指出一些我没有的问题
want to leave you with the impression
希望给您留下深刻的印象
that these are problems only with BCG
这些只是卡介苗的问题
but in general these are things that one
但总的来说，这些是
should think about before making a
在制作之前应该考虑一下
choice of mechanism
机制的选择